LASHA GOCHIASHVILI

I.gochiashvili@gmail.com • (+34) 677 870 456 • Barcelona, ES • in tds







SUMMARY

 Experienced in Data Analytics, Marketing Automation & Data-Driven Project Management. Interests: Machine Learning, Marketing Analytics, Econometrics & Tech Consulting. 4+ years' experience in a global company. 2-year highly qualified worker's visa in Spain. 3-year Polish visa.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Proficient in: R, Shiny App, SQL, Oracle OBIEE, Oracle Eloqua, Qlik, Excel
- Worked in: Python, Flask, Selenium, Tableau, Salesforce, Google Data Studio, Power BI, Google Analytics

EXPERIENCE

Ingersoll Rand - Sr. Digital Marketing Analyst

03.2021 - Present | Barcelona, ES

- Driving metric focused culture across marketing org with standard work & reports
- Leading project to centralize marketing reporting across org in Qlik; Defining & building reporting solutions for new tools & services; Owing closed loop reporting process; Providing general marketing support
- Implementing ML to improve lead generation/conversion

Ingersoll Rand – Digital Marketing Analyst

04.2019 - 2021.03 | Warsaw, PL

- Built and maintained marketing reporting for yearly 40 campaigns, 100mln+ marketing funnel, NPS surveys; Reporting for 7 main and 23 secondary KPIs, 12 P&Ls, 300+ users from junior specialists to VP level, Global coverage
- Coordinated & built reporting in Qlik from scratch to CXO level reports; Hosted weekly marketing update meetings attended by 12 P&L marketing leaders; Provided trainings to regional hubs in reporting; Coaching new teammates
- Main tools: Oracle Eloqua, OBIEE, Qlik, Salesforce, Excel, R

Gardner Denver – Data Analyst (merged with Ingersoll Rand)

12.2016 - 03.2019 | Warsaw, PL

- Grew prospects & customers database from 100k to 800k in <1 year via external and internal sources
- Coordinated first life-cycle campaign launch & installed-base database collection, 10k installed machines
- Supported in-house CRM roll out throughout the EMEA & APAC teams, 300+ sales reps

PROJECTS

Web Scraping in Selenium, Python. Created automated web scraper. Collected data to create chart with pollution levels in EU countries in 2020. Featured by Towards Data Science in Top Stories



- Interactive Web Dashboard in Shiny App, R. Created dashboard based on graduate survey data of Singapore to help young people choose right university/program in SG
- Clustering with K-means, R. Created clustering project for e-commerce customers to have better
- segmentation for further marketing campaigns



Machine Learning Model, R. Created ML predictions for bank customers' conversion to increase ROI

EDUCATION

University of Barcelona (exch. semester) - MA in Foundations of Data Science

2021 | Barcelona, ES

• Selected courses: Recommenders; NLP; Computer Vision; DS in Healthcare; Analysis of Complex Networks

University of Warsaw – MA in Data Science and Business Analytics

2019-2021 | Warsaw, PL

■ 1st year – 4.1/5.0 GPA; Selected courses: Machine Learning using Python & R, Data Structures and Algorithms, Data Mining, Big Data Analytics, Advanced Statistics, Econometrics & Economics

University of Lodz – MA in International Marketing

2014-2016 | Lodz, PL

4.4/5.0 GPA; Full study scholarship from European Commission; Won twice the best project/presentation in Advertising & Marketing Communications. Developed Google AdWords campaign for Lodz Film School

Tbilisi State University – BBA

2008-2012 | Tbilisi, GE

3.7/4.0 GPA; With Hons; Scholarship from the government of Georgia for outstanding undergraduate students

LANGUAGES

English	Georgian Georgian	Spanish Spanish	Russian -	Polish ———
---------------------------	-------------------	-----------------	-----------	------------